[{"answer": "What can I get for you ladies", "docId": "10-04", "aSentId": 12, "question": "", "qSentId": 11},{"answer": " Ill have a glass of the house white wine and my friend would like a Rum an", "docId": "10-04", "aSentId": 13, "question": "What can I get for you ladies", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": " OK.  Thatll be $8", "docId": "10-04", "aSentId": 17, "question": " Ill have a glass of the house white wine and my friend would like a Rum an", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": " Thank you.  Heres a $10.  Keep the change", "docId": "10-04", "aSentId": 18, "question": " OK.  Thatll be $8", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " So, what have you been up to this week", "docId": "10-04", "aSentId": 19, "question": " Thank you.  Heres a $10.  Keep the change", "qSentId": 18},{"answer": " Not much.  Just working.  Ive been trying to exercise more, so I went to the gy", "docId": "10-04", "aSentId": 20, "question": " So, what have you been up to this week", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " Thats great.  What are you doing there", "docId": "10-04", "aSentId": 24, "question": " Not much.  Just working.  Ive been trying to exercise more, so I went to the gy", "qSentId": 23},{"answer": " Just trying to tone up.    Ive been using the weight machines", "docId": "10-04", "aSentId": 25, "question": " Thats great.  What are you doing there", "qSentId": 24},{"answer": " Which gym do you go to", "docId": "10-04", "aSentId": 26, "question": " Just trying to tone up.    Ive been using the weight machines", "qSentId": 25},{"answer": " I go to the gym at the university.  Its pretty nice", "docId": "10-04", "aSentId": 30, "question": " Which gym do you go to", "qSentId": 29},{"answer": " Thats what I heard.  Its pretty big, right", "docId": "10-04", "aSentId": 31, "question": " I go to the gym at the university.  Its pretty nice", "qSentId": 30},{"answer": " Yeah, its big, and its a nice place", "docId": "10-04", "aSentId": 32, "question": " Thats what I heard.  Its pretty big, right", "qSentId": 31},{"answer": " Well, you look great", "docId": "10-04", "aSentId": 33, "question": " Yeah, its big, and its a nice place", "qSentId": 32},{"answer": " Thanks!  What have you been up to", "docId": "10-04", "aSentId": 34, "question": " Well, you look great", "qSentId": 33},{"answer": " Ive just been working too.  Oh, I forgot to tell you.  We got a kitten this week", "docId": "10-04", "aSentId": 35, "question": " Thanks!  What have you been up to", "qSentId": 34},{"answer": "  A kitten?  Where did you get it", "docId": "10-04", "aSentId": 36, "question": " Ive just been working too.  Oh, I forgot to tell you.  We got a kitten this week", "qSentId": 35},{"answer": " Our friends cat had babies and she couldnt keep them all, so we took one", "docId": "10-04", "aSentId": 37, "question": "  A kitten?  Where did you get it", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": " What color is he?  or She", "docId": "10-04", "aSentId": 38, "question": " Our friends cat had babies and she couldnt keep them all, so we took one", "qSentId": 37},{"answer": " Its a she.  She is black and white.  Her face is black, and the fur on her body i", "docId": "10-04", "aSentId": 39, "question": " What color is he?  or She", "qSentId": 38},{"answer": " Sounds cute", "docId": "10-04", "aSentId": 43, "question": " Its a she.  She is black and white.  Her face is black, and the fur on her body i", "qSentId": 42},{"answer": " Shes really cute.  We just have to make sure she doesnt scratch our furniture", "docId": "10-04", "aSentId": 44, "question": " Sounds cute", "qSentId": 43},{"answer": " Yeah, kittens can have sharp claws", "docId": "10-04", "aSentId": 45, "question": " Shes really cute.  We just have to make sure she doesnt scratch our furniture", "qSentId": 44},{"answer": " Hows your dog", "docId": "10-04", "aSentId": 46, "question": " Yeah, kittens can have sharp claws", "qSentId": 45},{"answer": " Hes good.  Hes about a year and a half now", "docId": "10-04", "aSentId": 47, "question": " Hows your dog", "qSentId": 46},{"answer": " How big is he", "docId": "10-04", "aSentId": 48, "question": " Hes good.  Hes about a year and a half now", "qSentId": 47},{"answer": " He weighs about 60 pounds now.  Hes pretty big", "docId": "10-04", "aSentId": 49, "question": " How big is he", "qSentId": 48},{"answer": " I think a dog is probably harder to take care of than a cat", "docId": "10-04", "aSentId": 50, "question": " He weighs about 60 pounds now.  Hes pretty big", "qSentId": 49},{"answer": " Yeah, cats are easy.  You just feed them.  A dog needs walks and requires mor", "docId": "10-04", "aSentId": 51, "question": " I think a dog is probably harder to take care of than a cat", "qSentId": 50},{"answer": " I think youre right", "docId": "10-04", "aSentId": 55, "question": " Yeah, cats are easy.  You just feed them.  A dog needs walks and requires mor", "qSentId": 54},{"answer": "Excuse me, ladies.  Am I in heaven because you look like angels", "docId": "10-04", "aSentId": 56, "question": " I think youre right", "qSentId": 55},{"answer": " Sigh No, youre not in heaven.  This is The Green Bar", "docId": "10-04", "aSentId": 57, "question": "Excuse me, ladies.  Am I in heaven because you look like angels", "qSentId": 56},{"answer": " You two are so beautiful.  I thought you were angels", "docId": "10-04", "aSentId": 61, "question": " Sigh No, youre not in heaven.  This is The Green Bar", "qSentId": 60},{"answer": " Yeah, right", "docId": "10-04", "aSentId": 62, "question": " You two are so beautiful.  I thought you were angels", "qSentId": 61},{"answer": " So what are your names", "docId": "10-04", "aSentId": 63, "question": " Yeah, right", "qSentId": 62},{"answer": " Umm, Im Sara and this is my friend Carla", "docId": "10-04", "aSentId": 64, "question": " So what are your names", "qSentId": 63},{"answer": " Nice to meet you.  Im Fred", "docId": "10-04", "aSentId": 65, "question": " Umm, Im Sara and this is my friend Carla", "qSentId": 64},{"answer": " Hi", "docId": "10-04", "aSentId": 66, "question": " Nice to meet you.  Im Fred", "qSentId": 65},{"answer": " Im a player for the Boston basketball team", "docId": "10-04", "aSentId": 67, "question": " Hi", "qSentId": 66},{"answer": " You?  Please, dont lie to us", "docId": "10-04", "aSentId": 68, "question": " Im a player for the Boston basketball team", "qSentId": 67},{"answer": " Im serious", "docId": "10-04", "aSentId": 69, "question": " You?  Please, dont lie to us", "qSentId": 68},{"answer": " OK", "docId": "10-04", "aSentId": 70, "question": " Im serious", "qSentId": 69},{"answer": " So do you two come here often", "docId": "10-04", "aSentId": 71, "question": " OK", "qSentId": 70},{"answer": " Occasionally", "docId": "10-04", "aSentId": 72, "question": " So do you two come here often", "qSentId": 71},{"answer": " Sometimes", "docId": "10-04", "aSentId": 73, "question": " Occasionally", "qSentId": 72},{"answer": " Ive never seen you before", "docId": "10-04", "aSentId": 74, "question": " Sometimes", "qSentId": 73},{"answer": "  Look, Fred.  If you dont mind, wed just like to talk alone tonight.  We hav", "docId": "10-04", "aSentId": 75, "question": " Ive never seen you before", "qSentId": 74},{"answer": " We have boyfriends too", "docId": "10-04", "aSentId": 79, "question": "  Look, Fred.  If you dont mind, wed just like to talk alone tonight.  We hav", "qSentId": 78},{"answer": " All right.  Sorry.  Can I get your numbers", "docId": "10-04", "aSentId": 80, "question": " We have boyfriends too", "qSentId": 79},{"answer": " No", "docId": "10-04", "aSentId": 81, "question": " All right.  Sorry.  Can I get your numbers", "qSentId": 80},{"answer": " You two angels have a good night", "docId": "10-04", "aSentId": 82, "question": " No", "qSentId": 81},{"answer": " Bye", "docId": "10-04", "aSentId": 83, "question": " You two angels have a good night", "qSentId": 82},{"answer": " Ew!  He was so gross", "docId": "10-04", "aSentId": 84, "question": " Bye", "qSentId": 83},{"answer": " I know.  A basketball player?  He looked like he was about 60", "docId": "10-04", "aSentId": 85, "question": " Ew!  He was so gross", "qSentId": 84},{"answer": " Hee hee!  I know.  I guess we angels are too irresistible", "docId": "10-04", "aSentId": 86, "question": " I know.  A basketball player?  He looked like he was about 60", "qSentId": 85}]
